mozo.com.au 2019-12-28

# Mozo Privacy Policy | Mozo

## Introduction

Mozo respects and upholds the confidentiality and privacy of individuals. Mozo is committed to ensuring the privacy of personal information you provide to us. We are bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) and guided by the Australian Privacy Principles. Mozo wants to make you aware how we collect, use, disclose and store your personal information.

This Privacy Policy outlines our practices relating to the collection of information collected through all our services, website, widgets, competitions, customer surveys (collectively, the "Services"). By using any of the Services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to all persons who interact with Mozo including those that are financial providers with commercial relationships with Mozo, registered users and unregistered users of the Services. Unless you give us explicit consent otherwise, we will act in accordance with this Privacy Policy with regards to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of personal information.

## What information do we collect?

We will only collect personal information that is necessary for us to provide you with the Services that we offer. If you choose not to provide certain personal information then we may not be able to provide the Services to you. 

The following are the main types of personal information we collect and the main purpose for which that information is collected: 

### Personal information we collect 

The primary purpose for which we collect your personal information is to provide the services you request. This includes: 

  * Opt in to receive news, alerts, surveys and special offers from us 
  * Complete a customer review survey 
  * Provide us with feedback or complete one of our user surveys 
  * Complete inquiry forms requesting Mozo or third party providers, selected by you, contacting you 
  * Speak with us to discuss product information and request to be contacted by third party providers 
  * Obtain your credit score for the purpose of providing you with tailored loan pricing at your request 

This information, in most cases, will be your email address but may also be your name, phone number, postcode and information associated to your request. This information also includes other information that you may provide as part of your ongoing relationship with Mozo. 

If you authorise us to obtain your credit score we will ask you for additional identity information for the purpose of obtaining that score from a credit agency. This is typically your full name, address, date of birth, sex, and driver’s licence number. 

### Public information, post and commentary 

This information consists of any information that you make publicly available by completing a customer review survey for publication on the Mozo site. This information is public which will be available to everyone. 

### Site usage Information 

When you interact with Mozo we may collect certain bits of information about those visits. Cookies and other tracking data are pieces of information that our web page transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies do not personally identify you, only your computer browser. The type of information that may be collected and stored by Mozo includes your IP address, the date and time of your visit, the pages accessed, documents retrieved, your location, the device you're using, meta data, referring website and the links you've clicked on as you interact with Services. This information is collected in the course of the delivery of the Services to you so Mozo can better understand and improve the Services based on the way our services are being used. 

You can delete cookies from your computer at any time via your internet browser. However doing so may limit your use of some of Mozo's features. 

### Information in relation to other persons who deal with us 

We also collect personal information about individuals who are, or are employed by our suppliers, customers, contractors and related companies. When we collect this information we will generally indicate why we are collecting this personal information when we collect it and how we plan to use it, or it will be obvious how we intend to use it at the time we are collecting this information. 

## How do we use your information? 

We use the information we collect about you in order to provide the Services to you. These uses include: 

  * To analyse our website visitors and their usage to enhance our Services 
  * Communicating with you via email where you have elected to receive newsletters, special offers, competitions and survey requests from Mozo 
  * Communicating with you via phone where you have elected to have Mozo contact you in this manner 
  * To facilitate third party's contacting you where you have provided your consent as part of the Service 
  * Collecting and displaying customer reviews information, individually and in aggregate, you have provided as part of the Service 
  * To deliver relevant advertisements to you and provide information about us, our Services and special offers 
  * To provide information to 3rd party service providers so they can deliver relevant advertisements to you 
  * To carry out the administrative and operational functions of the Mozo business 
  * To carry out research services provided to Mozo customers 
  * To respond to inquiries 
  * To undertake internal accounting and administration 
  * To provide you with customised rate information based on your credit score, where you have asked us to do so 

Where we ask for personal information we clearly outline the purpose for which the information is collected and how we will use your information and to whom it may be disclosed. We will only use your personal information as required to provide the functions and Services you request and will do so in a transparent manner. By providing personal information to Mozo on our website or via the phone, you authorise and consent to Mozo collecting, using, storing and disclosing personal information about you as described in this Privacy Policy. 

If you request that your personal information is passed onto another entity by using our Services we will share your personal information with that third party. Once we disclose your personal information to a third party we are no longer responsible for the conduct or practices of those third party providers, as they are not under our control. When you are contacted by a third-party you should check the applicable privacy policy of that third party. 

We use third party service providers in order to provide the Services to you and in doing so may make your information available to certain third party service providers. These services include website hosting, mailing list providers, CRM software, accounting software, web analytics software, ad serving and online marketing software. These providers may be located in a range of different countries including Australia and the United States. We take all steps which are reasonable in the circumstances to ensure that these organisations both inside and outside of Australia deal with personal information according to this Privacy Policy and do not breach the Australian Privacy Principles in relation to the information. 

We may also use the information provided by you on an anonymous basis where your personal information is not identifiable and we may use this for any purpose or share it with third parties. We mainly use your information on this basis in relation to our market research services, measuring the way that our Services are being used and the publishing of customer reviews information on the site. We may also provide this information to 3rd parties to allow them to serve relevant advertisements to you. 

## How do we protect your information? 

Mozo will act to protect your personal information in accordance with the Australian Privacy Principles using commercially reasonable administrative and technical measures to safeguard and protect this information. We are committed to keeping the personal information you provide to us secure. We take all reasonable precautions to protect the personal information we hold about you from misuse and loss and from misuse, interference, loss, unauthorised access, modification or disclosure. 

We will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information if it is no longer needed for the purpose for which the information was disclosed or lawfully required. 

We will only collect your personal information by lawful and fair means. 

## Accessing or correcting your information 

We provide you with easy access to the personal information we hold about you. Once you register you can easily access and change your personal information by contacting Mozo directly. If you require details of your personal information held by us, we will need to verify your identity before meeting your request, which we will process in a reasonable time. 

If the information we hold about you is inaccurate, irrelevant, misleading, incomplete or outdated, inform us so that we can promptly correct it. 

If you no longer wish to receive email communications from us, you can unsubscribe at any time by using the link on the emails we send you, or informing us and we will do it for you. Our marketing communications will provide you with details of how to opt-out. 

You can delete cookies from your computer at any time via your internet browser. However doing so will limit your use of some of Mozo's features. 

When your personal information is no longer needed, or if it not collected from you personally and it would not be lawful for us to collect it, we will remove any personal identifiers or we will ensure the secure destruction of the records. 

As far as permissible under law, Mozo accepts no responsibility for the unauthorised access of personal information held by Mozo. 

## Other important information for you 

### Consent

By communicating with Mozo, including by submitting information through Mozo's websites, you consent to the information you provide being collected, stored, used and disclosed by us in accordance with our Privacy Policy. 

### Updates to Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on 6 February 2019. 

Mozo may update this Privacy Policy from time to time as it enhances the Mozo Service. Any changes that Mozo makes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the Privacy Policy. You should periodically visit this page to review the current Privacy Policy. 

### Location of Data 

Some of Mozo services are hosted and managed outside of Australia and in using the Services you consent to having any personal information accessible from or transmitted outside of Australia. 

### Links to other sites 

Mozo provides you with links from our site to other third party sites. Once you transfer from the Mozo website to another website, we are not responsible for the conduct or practices of those third party websites, as they are not under our control. When you transfer to another website you should check the applicable privacy policy of that site. 

### Anonymity and pseudonymity 

You have the right to anonymity, or to use a pseudonym when dealing with us, and you do not have to supply us with information, however if you choose not to provide the information and we need to fulfil your request for a specific Service, we may be unable to provide you with that requested Service. 

### Data Retention 

We will retain any information collected for the period necessary for us to fulfil the purpose for which it was collected as outlined in this Privacy Policy. If the law requires a longer retention period then we will retain the information as dictated by law. We may also retain backup information of personal information we have collected from you under this Privacy Policy. This information may be retained for the purposes of complying with applicable laws or our own security policies. We do not always complete remove or delete all of your information due to technical and system constraints along with contractual, financial or legal requirements. Identity information provided for the purpose of obtaining a credit score will only be used for the authorised purpose and not retained by Mozo. 

### Complaints 

If you have a complaint about a breach of the Privacy Act then please contact us via the contact details outlined below. When you contact us please provide us with the necessary contact details so that we can get response to you, along with a brief description of the complaint. If you are not satisfied with the outcome of our response you can refer your complaint to the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner (www.oaic.gov.au). 

##  How you can contact us 

If you have any queries in relation to this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to request access to your personal information or have a complaint about a breach of privacy, then please contact us at: 

Email: 

| 

privacy@mozo.com.au   
  
---|---  
  
Mail: 

| 

Privacy Compliance Officer 

Mozo Pty Ltd 

Level 10, 89 York St 

Sydney NSW 2000   
  
Phone: 

| 

02 9037 4366   
  
Mozo provides factual information in relation to financial products. While Mozo attempts to make a wide range of products and providers available via its site it may not cover all the options available to you. The information published on Mozo is general in nature only and does not consider your personal objectives, financial situation or particular needs and is not recommending any particular product to you. Mozo is paid by product issuers for clicks on, or applications for, products marked as "Promoted". If you decide to apply for a product you will be dealing directly with that provider and not with Mozo. Mozo recommends that you read the relevant PDS or offer documentation before taking up any financial product offer. For more information please see Mozo's FSG, General advice disclaimer or Terms of use.

_mozo.com.au_ © Copyright 2008-2019 Mozo Pty Ltd. All Rights Reserved. ABN: 68 128 199 208. AFSL & ACL 328141
